(Mrs Cooper:)Shelly, I'm so proud of you and
Leonard for getting this award.
(Sheldon:)Oh, thank you, Mother.
(Mrs Cooper:)I tried to read your paper,
but it was very hard
(Mrs Cooper:)for me to understand.
(Sheldon:)Oh, it's quite
straightforward, actually.
(Sheldon:)It describes a new model
of the universe
(Sheldon:)that conceptualizes it
as the surface
(Sheldon:)of an n-dimensional
superfluid.
(Mrs Cooper:)Interesting.
(Mrs Cooper:)You can believe that,
(Mrs Cooper:)but God filling an ark with
animals two-by-two is nonsense.
(Sheldon:)What did they feed
the lions, Mother?
(Mrs Cooper:)The floating bodies of
drowned sinners, of course.
(Sheldon:)Listen, Leonard's mom is
a renowned psychiatrist
(Sheldon:)and woman of science.
(Sheldon:)Can you please keep
the Bible babble to yourself
(Sheldon:)while she's here?
(Mrs Cooper:)Are you ashamed of me?
(Sheldon:)Of course not.
I love you.
(Sheldon:)I'm just embarrassed by the
things you believe, do and say.